The following content is provided
提供以下内容
under a Creative Commons license.
根据知识共享许可。
Your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue
您的支持将帮助MIT OpenCourseWare继续
to offer high quality educational resources for free.
免费提供高质量的教育资源。
To make a donation or view additional materials
捐款或查看其他材料
from hundreds of MIT courses, visit MIT OpenCourseWare
从数百门麻省理工学院的课程中，访问MIT OpenCourseWare
at ocw.mit.edu.
在ocw.mit.edu。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So who's going lecture?
那谁去上课？
Good.
好。
Does everything makes sense?
一切都有意义吗？
AUDIENCE: Mostly.
听众：主要是。
PROFESSOR: That's good, because we're going to do problems.
教授：很好，因为我们要解决问题。
AUDIENCE: Awesome.
听众：太棒了。
PROFESSOR: So, what I want to talk about is, first,
教授：所以，我首先要谈的是
there's a subtlety in the Rubik's cube problem, which I'm
我在魔方问题中有一个微妙之处
guessing nobody has seen yet, but we're going to talk about
猜测还没有人见过，但我们将要谈论
it anyway, because otherwise you'll trip on it while you're
无论如何，因为否则您会在旅途中绊倒
doing the problem.
做问题。
And then we're going to talk about one or maybe two
然后我们要谈一两个
problems.
问题。
And I'm excited about the problem titled,
我很高兴看到这个标题的问题，
"there's StarCraft and counter strikes,"
“有《星际争霸》和反恐精英，”
so, let's hope we get to them.
所以，我们希望我们能找到他们。
AUDIENCE: I'm curious, did you write this week's problem set?
听众：我很好奇，你写了这周的习题集吗？
Because there's some Chinese in there.
因为那里有一些中国人。
PROFESSOR: No.
教授：不。
AUDIENCE: Oh, OK.
听众：哦，好。
PROFESSOR: No, someone else wrote it.
教授：不，是别人写的。
I suggested putting that in there, though.
我建议把它放在那里。
AUDIENCE: You had an awesome internship, right?
听众：你有一个很棒的实习吧？
[INAUDIBLE]
[听不清]
AUDIENCE: Wait, did you make all the AMD [INAUDIBLE] questions?
听众：等等，您是否提出了所有AMD [音频不清晰]问题？
PROFESSOR:Of course.
教授：当然可以。
That's my stuff.
那是我的东西。
OK.
好。
So Rubik's cubes.
因此，鲁比克的立方体。
Did everyone see a 2 by 2 by 2 Rubik's cube?
每个人都看到2 x 2 x 2 Rubik的立方体吗？
You guys are going to lecture, right?
你们要去听课吧？
You have one.
你有一个。
Yeah.
是的
Did you guys see Eric's 2 by 2 by 2 Rubik's cube?
你们看到过Eric的2 x 2 x 2 Rubik立方体吗？
It looks sort of like this.
看起来像这样。
All right, so big Rubik's cube has how many
好吧，这么大的魔方有多少个
small cubelets in it?
里面有小方块？
AUDIENCE: 80.
听众：80。
AUDIENCE: I like cubelets better than cubies.
听众：我比立方体更喜欢立方体。
Cubies is hard to say.
多维数据集很难说。
PROFESSOR: Yeah, I would say cubicles.
教授：是的，我要说隔间。
So let's go for-- let's try cubelets
所以我们去尝试一下
and see how this works.
并查看其工作原理。
OK.
好。
So each cubelet has six faces, but three faces
所以每个立方体有六个面，但是三个面
are always facing inwards.
总是向内。
They're always attached to the center of the cube.
它们始终附着在立方体的中心。
So we don't care about them.
所以我们不在乎他们。
We only care about the other three faces.
我们只关心其他三个面孔。
So if you have a plastic Rubik's cube.
因此，如果您有塑料魔方。
Say this is a plastic-- This is a plastic cube.
说这是塑料-这是塑料立方体。
Then you're going to have eight plastic cubelets.
然后，您将拥有八个塑料立方体。
Each cubelet has three colored faces
每个立方体都有三个彩色的面
and three faces that we don't care about.
和我们不关心的三张脸。
So how many total plastic faces in a cubelet, sorry,
那么，一个立方体中有多少塑料面，对不起，
plastic cube?
塑料立方体？
AUDIENCE: Twenty-four. [INAUDIBLE]
听众：二十四岁。 [听不清]
PROFESSOR: All right.
教授：好的。
Now let's play with an imaginary cube.
现在让我们玩一个假想的立方体。
And I call this a wireframe cube,
我称其为线框立方体
because I draw it like this.
因为我是这样画的
So, here pretend you have the skeleton of a Rubik's cube,
因此，这里假设您拥有魔方的骨架，
made out of wires or out of wood or something.
用电线或木头或其他东西制成。
So it's basically a small sheet of wood, small piece of wood,
所以基本上是一小块木头，一小块木头，
small sheet of wood, so on and so forth.
小片木头，依此类推。
And so this doesn't have any colors in it,
因此，其中没有任何颜色，
but it's the right shape and sort of the right look.
但这是正确的形状和正确的外观。
So the way you would build the configuration is,
因此，您构建配置的方式是
you take 24 plastic faces that you get from a plastic cube,
你从塑料立方体上取了24个塑料面，
and you paste them one by one onto the faces
然后将它们一一粘贴到脸上
of a wireframe cube.
线框多维数据集。
And they claim that this can build any configuration
他们声称这可以建立任何配置
that you can think about.
您可以考虑的。
If you look at a cube, after no matter how many moves
如果看一个立方体，无论移动多少
you've done to it, it's going to have
你已经做到了，它将有
some-- it's going to have the faces somewhere, right?
一些-到处都会有面孔，对吧？
So you can take the faces and face them
这样你就可以面对他们
where they belong and there you go.
他们属于哪里，你去了那里。
You have a real cube built out of a wireframe
您具有使用线框构建的真实立方体
and plastic faces.
和塑料的面孔。
How many wireframe faces there are?
有多少个线框面？
Please don't get this wrong.
请不要误解。
AUDIENCE: Twenty-four.
听众：二十四岁。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
AUDIENCE: There are some configurations
听众：有一些配置
that aren't possible, right?
那是不可能的，对吧？
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
There are some configurations that aren't possible,
有些配置是不可能的，
and that is very good news.
这是一个好消息。
We'll get to that later.
我们稍后再讨论。
Let's see how the code talks about these faces.
让我们看看代码如何谈论这些面孔。
So suppose we have a cubelet that has these faces.
因此，假设我们有一个具有这些面的立方体。
Front faces yellow, this face is blue, and this face is orange.
正面为黄色，正面为蓝色，正面为橙色。
This facing code is called-- so this yellow face here
这个面对的代码被称为-所以这里的黄脸
is called y o b.
被称为哟b。
So y is yellow, that's the yellow face,
y是黄色，那是黄色的脸，
and is the yellow facing the cubelet that
面对立方体的黄色是
has a yellow face, an orange face, and a blue face.
有一张黄色的脸，一张橙色的脸和一张蓝色的脸。
Fortunately, there aren't two cubelets
幸运的是，没有两个立方体
that have the same face color, so this is good enough
具有相同的脸色，所以就足够了
to distinguish between all of them.
区分所有人。
Let's see if you guys are paying attention.
让我们看看你们是否在关注。
How would I call this face?
我怎么称呼这张脸？
AUDIENCE: o y b?
听众：oyb？
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
Either that or o b y, whichever one the code happens to use.
要么顺从，要么碰巧使用该代码。
So the principal is, these are the colors
所以原理是，这些是颜色
and the first one is the face that you're pointing at.
第一个是您要指向的脸。
So there are 24 plastic faces, so there
所以有24个塑料面
are 24 names for these plastic faces.
这些塑料面孔的24个名称。
Let's see how we name the wireframe faces.
让我们看看如何命名线框面。
If I take this face-- so we don't have colors here,
如果我采取这张脸-所以我们这里没有颜色，
they're all the same.
他们都是一样的。
So instead we care about their position.
因此，我们关心他们的位置。
A cube has a front and a back, right?
立方体有正面和背面，对吗？
This cubelet is on the front somewhere, right?
这个立方体在前面的某个地方，对不对？
So I'm going to have front somewhere in the name.
因此，我将在名称中占据领先位置。
It has an upper face and a lower face.
它具有上表面和下表面。
Is this going to be upper or lower?
这是较高还是较低？
AUDIENCE: Upper.
听众：上层。
PROFESSOR: And the left or right?
教授：那是左还是右？
PROFESSOR: Right.
教授：对。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So front upper right, which face am I looking at?
那么右上角，我在看哪张脸？
AUDIENCE: The front.
听众：前面。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
f u r, fur.
皮毛
How about this space?
这个空间怎么样？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: So far so good?
教授：到目前为止还好吗？
Or it could be r u f, right?
还是可能是ruf，对吗？
PROFESSOR: Or it could be r u f.
教授：或者可能是ru f。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: I really don't know what it means, I'm behind.
教授：我真的不知道这意味着什么，我落后了。
AUDIENCE: Ruff like a dog?
听众：像狗一样吹牛？
It has fur.
它有皮毛。
PROFESSOR: Oh, ruff ruff ruff.
教授：哦，,！
OK.
好。
That's not too bad.
还算不错
I was afraid of something worse.
我害怕更糟的事情。
OK.
好。
That's cool.
这很酷。
So a configuration will take plastic faces
因此，配置将采用塑料表面
and face them onto the wireframe faces.
并将它们面对在线框表面上。
So a configuration is going to be an array of 24 elements.
因此，配置将由24个元素组成。
And the first element is going to tell me which plastic face
第一个要告诉我的是塑料脸
ends up in-- Let's say if you are the second one,
结束于-假设您是第二个，
says which plastic face ends up in r u f,
说出哪些塑料面最终变成棕褐色，
and the third one, let's assume it's the space.
第三个，我们假设它是空间。
AUDIENCE: Ruff.
听众：鲁夫。
PROFESSOR: Ruff.
教授：鲁夫。
And there are 21 more faces, right?
还有21张脸，对吗？
So each face has a number from zero
所以每个脸都有一个从零开始的数字
to 23, because we're in Python, so we like zero-based indexing.
到23，因为我们在Python中，所以我们喜欢从零开始的索引。
And 24 elements in the array, 24 plastic faces.
阵列中有24个元素，有24个塑料面。
Which plastic face goes into f u r?
哪个塑料面会进入毛皮？
Assuming this cubelet here-- see, I said cubicle anyway.
假设这里有这个小立方体，反正我还是说小隔间。
This cubelet here goes here in exactly this configuration.
此处的多维数据集正是以这种配置在此处运行的。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
So this face ends up here.
因此，这张脸在这里结束。
And that's what it means that the first element in the array
这就是数组中的第一个元素
is y o b.
是b。
How about r u f?
ruf怎么样？
Who ends up in r u f?
谁最终变成了ruf？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
AUDIENCE: B o y.
听众：拜拜。
PROFESSOR: And who ends up in e r f?
教授：谁最终以erf告终？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So does everyone understand configurations?
那么每个人都了解配置吗？
Does this make sense?
这有意义吗？
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
I got lost somewhere in there.
我迷路了。
Can you explain the order for f u r and [INAUDIBLE]?
您能解释一下皮草和[听不清]的顺序吗？
Like front upright?
像前柱一样吗？
PROFESSOR: Oh.
教授：哦。
So do you mean-- so the order of the letters.
所以你的意思是-字母的顺序。
So there are two orderings here.
因此，这里有两个排序。
One is the order of the letters and there is an order.
一个是字母的顺序，然后是一个顺序。
I think the code uses clockwise order,
我认为代码使用顺时针顺序，
but what really matters is the first letter tells you which
但真正重要的是第一个字母告诉您
face you're talking about.
面对你在谈论。
AUDIENCE: So this is front face.
听众：这是正面。
PROFESSOR: Face, up face.
教授：面朝上。
AUDIENCE: What's up?
听众：怎么了？
What's front?
前面是什么？
PROFESSOR: So for this cubelet, this is front,
教授：所以对于这个立方体，这是最前面的，
this is the right, this is up.
这是正确的，这是向上。
This cubelet wold have a front, an up, and a left.
这块立方体有一个正面，一个上方和一个左侧。
So now there are 24 faces and all
所以现在有24张脸
of them get numbers from 0 23.
他们从0 23。
And here we assume that f u r is space zero,
这里我们假设毛发是零空间
r u f is space 1, and e r f is face 2, which
ruf是空间1，而erf是面2，
is not quite [INAUDIBLE], but you'll have the mapping there.
还不是[音频不清晰]，但是您将在其中找到映射。
OK.
好。
So a configuration is in an array of 24 elements
因此，配置包含24个元素
and it maps plastic faces to wireframe faces, which
并将塑料面映射到线框面
brings us to, how many configurations are there?
带我们到那里，有多少种配置？
AUDIENCE: You mean like mapping 4 factorial?
听众：您是说喜欢映射4阶乘？
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So let's see what it does.
因此，让我们看看它的作用。
We have 24 plastic faces.
我们有24个塑料面。
From 0 to 23.
从0到23。
And they have to be mapped to 24 positions.
并且必须将它们映射到24个位置。
AUDIENCE: [INTERPOSING VOICES]
听众：[插入语音]
AUDIENCE: There's six colors, aren't there?
听众：有六种颜色，不是吗？
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: There are six colors, but if this is also yellow,
教授：有六种颜色，但如果也是黄色，
but there's a red here.
但是这里有红色。
This is a different face, see, this is yellow,
这是一张不同的脸，看，这是黄色的，
red, and there's a green down here.
红色，这里有绿色。
Then this is the yellow face of the yellow, green, red cubelet.
这是黄色，绿色，红色立方体的黄色面。
So we care about the individual faces.
因此，我们关心个人面孔。
So yeah, your answer was right.
是的，您的答案是正确的。
I'm trying to explain it to everyone else.
我正在尝试向其他人解释。
But your answer is right.
但是你的答案是正确的。
AUDIENCE: Well, wait.
听众：好吧，等等。
But you can't-- I mean, we talk about some are impossible.
但是您不能-我的意思是，我们谈论一些不可能的事情。
Like, you're always gonna have a grouping of y o b.
就像，您总是会有一组yo b。
That's never gonna change.
那永远不会改变。
PROFESSOR: Right.
教授：对。
So some of these aren't reachable,
所以其中一些是无法达到的，
because you're not allowed to break up the cube.
因为不允许您分解多维数据集。
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: And that's OK.
教授：没关系。
This is still how the code represents them.
这仍然是代码表示它们的方式。
So I'm asking if you had-- if all these would be possible,
所以我问你是否有-如果所有这些都可能，
how many would we get?
我们会得到多少？
And the answer is that to map 24 plastic faces
答案是要映射24个塑料面
to 24 wireframe faces.
到24个线框面。
So this mapping is called-- anyone good with math?
因此，这种映射称为-擅长数学的人吗？
AUDIENCE: 1 to 1.
观众：1比1。
AUDIENCE: Bijection.
听众：双射。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So when you're taking-- OK.
所以，当您服用时-好。
So when we have two sets and you have a bijection between them
所以当我们有两个集合，而你在两个集合之间有一个双射
or 1 to 1 mapping, that function is also called?
或1对1映射，该函数也称为？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: You probably don't know the answer yet.
教授：您可能还不知道答案。
You have to wait until the end of 6042.
您必须等到6042结束。
So I'm trying to hint that right now, if you remember
所以我现在想暗示一下，如果您还记得的话
the end of 6042, maybe the answer is somewhere there.
6042年末，也许答案就在那儿。
AUDIENCE: Blur?.
听众：模糊吗？
AUDIENCE: Perfect.
听众：完美。
AUDIENCE: A perfect match
观众：完美的搭配
AUDIENCE: Permut--.
听众：排列-
AUDIENCE: I totally learned about that in middle school,
听众：我在中学时就完全了解了这一点，
I think.
我认为。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So this is--
所以这是-
AUDIENCE: Permutations and combinations.
听众：排列和组合。
PROFESSOR: So this is a permutation.
教授：这是一个排列。
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: How many permutations do you have out of 24 elements?
教授：您有24个元素中有多少个排列？
AUDIENCE: Does that order [? mean ?] [? matters ?]
听众：命令吗？意思 ？] [？有关系吗？]
[INAUDIBLE] 24 [INAUDIBLE].
[听不清] 24 [听不清]。
PROFESSOR: So this is a lot of permutations, right?
教授：因此，这是很多排列的，对吗？
It's a good thing that we're not going
我们不去是一件好事
to explore most of these configurations.
探索其中的大多数配置。
So we said before, that we're going
所以我们之前说过，我们要
to build a graph where the vertices are configurations,
在顶点为配置的情况下构建图，
and the edges are moves that get us
边缘是使我们前进的动作
from one configuration to another configuration.
从一种配置到另一种配置。
Can they afford to build this graph first and then run
他们能否负担得起先构建此图然后运行
BFS on it?
BFS就可以了吗？
Not going to work, right?
不上班吧？
We don't have enough RAM for this.
我们没有足够的RAM用于此。
So instead we're going to have to operate
所以相反，我们将不得不操作
on an implicit graph for presentation.
在用于表示的隐式图上。
Well, fortunately, BFS doesn't want the whole graph.
好吧，幸运的是，BFS不需要整个图表。
The way BFS works is it has a list of nodes
BFS的工作方式是它具有节点列表
that it has to visit, and when it visits a node,
它必须访问，并且当它访问节点时，
it wants to know its neighbors.
它想知道它的邻居。
And that's it.
就是这样。
Yes?
是？
Everyone happy with it?
每个人都满意吗？
So all they have to do is, in order
所以他们要做的就是
to build this implicit graph representation,
建立这个隐式图表示
is we have to know the start node,
是我们必须知道起始节点，
So BFS can start somewhere.
因此BFS可以从某个地方开始。
And we have to be able to give it a node,
而且我们必须能够给它一个节点，
we have to be able to generate all the neighbor nodes.
我们必须能够生成所有邻居节点。
So given the configuration, we have
所以给定配置，我们有
to be able to generate the configurations that
能够生成配置
would result by applying most of that configuration.
通过应用大多数该配置将得到结果。
So what are the moves that you can do with this?
那么，您可以采取哪些措施？
Suppose you have a cubelet.
假设您有一个立方体。
What are the possible moves?
有哪些可能的举动？
There aren't that many.
没有那么多。
We're interested in the simplest kind of moves.
我们对最简单的举动感兴趣。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE]
观众：[听不清]
AUDIENCE: Yeah, you can make the right side
听众：是的，你可以做右边
go right, which is equivalent to the left side going left.
向右走，相当于左侧向左走。
And then you can do [INAUDIBLE] 4, left [INAUDIBLE].
然后，您可以执行[听不清] 4，然后离开[听不清]。
AUDIENCE: It's a nice number.
听众：这是一个不错的数字。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
I think there are a few more, so here's how I look at it.
我想还有更多，所以这就是我的看法。
You can take the front face, so these four,
你可以把正面，所以这四个，
and do a clockwise rotation, 90 degrees,
然后顺时针旋转90度，
or you can do a counterclockwise rotation, 90 degrees.
或者您可以逆时针旋转90度。
And you can do that for each face.
您可以为每张脸做这些。
AUDIENCE: But doing a front clockwise rotation is the same
听众：但是顺时针旋转是一样的
as doing a back counter clockwise rotation, which
像逆时针旋转一样，
is [? it-- ?]
是[？它-？]
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: Doing a front clockwise,
教授：顺时针方向转动，
doing a back counterclockwise is the same thing
逆时针方向后退是一回事
after you account for symmetries.
在考虑对称性之后。
Yeah.
是的
AUDIENCE: Exactly.
听众：是的。
AUDIENCE: So it's six?
听众：是六点？
PROFESSOR: Yep.
教授：是的。
So there's only six after you account for symmetries.
因此，考虑对称性后只有六个。
Let's play devil's advocate and assume
让我们扮演魔鬼的拥护者并承担
we don't account for symmetries.
我们不考虑对称性。
We're actually doing the code, because I
我们实际上正在执行代码，因为我
need to teach you something.
需要教你一些东西。
So let's assume we don't apply.
因此，假设我们不适用。
By the way, how would you account
顺便问一下
for symmetries, easy way?
对于对称性，简单的方法？
Did anyone read the comments in the code?
是否有人阅读了代码中的注释？
OK.
好。
So would you account for symmetries.
因此，您会考虑对称性。
AUDIENCE: Doesn't it just happen?
听众：这不是真的吗？
The permutation is going to [INAUDIBLE].
排列将变为[音频不清晰]。
AUDIENCE: Can you just look at it,
听众：你能看看吗，
like, each space is neighboring faces, and [INAUDIBLE]?
例如，每个空间都是相邻的面孔，[听不清]？
PROFESSOR: So the way we do it is we anchor one cubelet.
教授：因此，我们的方法是锚定一个立方体。
So we have one cubelet that is a plastic cubelet that
因此，我们有一个塑料立方体，
is always going to go here.
总是要去这里。
So three plastic faces here are always
所以这里总是有三个塑料面
going to go to three wireframed faces here.
这里要去三个线框的面孔。
And if you fix those three faces then
如果修好这三张脸，
you don't have simple symmetries anymore.
您不再具有简单的对称性。
All right?
好吧？
Three axes of symmetry, so fixing three faces settles it.
三个对称轴，因此固定三个面即可解决它。
AUDIENCE: Wait, so then how many moves are possible?
听众：等等，那么可以移动几步呢？
12?
12点？
AUDIENCE: No.
听众：不。
But you only do one thing, though.
但是，您只能做一件事。
Now you don't do counterclock-- you don't do.
现在您不做时钟-您不做时钟。
AUDIENCE: If one is anchored, there's six left.
听众：如果锚定一个，则剩下六个。
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
Yeah.
是的
You don't move the anchored one.
您不会移动锚定的那个。
AUDIENCE: Oh yeah, because you can only [INAUDIBLE] two
听众：哦，是的，因为你只能[听不清]两个
of the-- three of the faces now, but.
其中的三个面孔，不过。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So let's look at the left face.
因此，让我们看一下左脸。
So you have a configuration.
这样便有了配置。
So you can move the left face clockwise,
这样您可以顺时针方向移动左脸，
left face counterclockwise.
左脸逆时针旋转。
You can move the top face clockwise, top face
您可以顺时针移动顶面
counterclockwise, and a couple more.
逆时针，还有更多。
So what does a move look like?
那么，举动看起来像什么？
Someone said it before.
有人说过
So when you're doing a move, what's going to happen is,
因此，当您采取行动时，将会发生的事情是，
a move doesn't create plastic faces
此举不会产生可塑的面孔
and it doesn't destroy them, right?
并不会摧毁它们，对不对？
It just changes their position on the wireframe.
它只是改变它们在线框上的位置。
So if you have an initial configuration that
因此，如果您具有初始配置，
has plastic faces assigned to wireframe faces,
将塑料面分配给线框面，
and you have a final configuration,
并完成了最终配置，
these plastic faces are going to end up somewhere
这些塑料面孔将最终消失在某个地方
on the wireframe.
在线框上。
And that's true for all the plastic faces.
所有塑料面都是这样。
So the plastic faces are going to end up somewhere.
因此，塑料面将最终出现在某处。
Also, what's nice is if we look at the wireframe,
而且，好的是，如果我们看一下线框，
if I do a clockwise rotation in the front, whatever
如果我在前面顺时针旋转，无论
plastic face was here is going to end up here.
塑料的脸在这里要在这里结束。
Whatever plastic face was here is going to end up here,
无论这里的塑料脸是什么，
so on and so forth.
等等等等。
So it's a function of rotation [INAUDIBLE] inside [INAUDIBLE].
因此，这是[听不清]内部旋转[听不清]的功能。
Like the four faces that correspond to each other,
就像彼此对应的四个脸一样，
rotate.
旋转。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
That's some good-- that's going deeper than want to go.
很好-比想去的要深入。
I want to account for something simpler.
我想解释一些简单的问题。
So my point is that the arrows will always,
所以我的意思是箭头将永远
if I do a right clockwise rotation,
如果我顺时针旋转，
the arrows will always look the same.
箭头将始终看起来相同。
So the only thing that changes is what's inside the array.
所以唯一改变的是数组内部。
But if you take one configuration array
但是，如果您采用一个配置阵列
and you move things according to the way you're
然后按照自己的方式移动事物
supposed to move them for the front clockwise move,
应该将它们向前顺时针移动，
you're going to get the right result.
您将获得正确的结果。
So what is this a bunch of arrows called?
那么这串箭叫什么呢？
What does it do?
它有什么作用？
What does it do to the faces?
它对脸有什么作用？
What does it do to the elements of the array?
它对数组的元素有什么作用？
AUDIENCE: It moves in different spots.
听众：它在不同的位置移动。
PROFESSOR: OK, so fancy math name?
教授：好的，那么漂亮的数学名称吗？
AUDIENCE: Shuffle.
听众：随机播放。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So this is what I got before.
这就是我以前得到的。
This is how you think of it, right?
您是怎么想的，对吗？
It's a shuffle, so fancy math name for a shuttle.
这是一个混洗，所以穿梭的数学名称如此奇特。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: All right.
教授：好的。
AUDIENCE: Something going on here.
听众：这里发生了什么。
PROFESSOR: So then a move is a?
教授：那么那是一个举动吗？
AUDIENCE: Rotation [? permutation?].
听众：轮换[？排列？]。
[INAUDIBLE]
[听不清]
PROFESSOR: All right, so the thing is-- the difficult part
教授：好的，这就是-困难的部分
of the code is you have two things that
代码的两点是
are represented by permutations.
用排列表示。
Configurations are permutations of plastic faces
配置是塑料面的排列
onto the array, onto the array of wireframes faces.
到线框面阵列上。
And then a move is a permutation of a configuration
然后移动就是配置的排列
into another configuration.
进入另一种配置。
OK, so now if I want to compute neighbors,
好，现在如果我要计算邻居，
I take-- we think there are six moves,
我认为-我们认为有六个动作，
so I'm going to take six moves.
所以我要采取六个动作。
I'm going to type out the permutations, so 6 times
我要输入排列，所以6次
24 numbers, and that's it.
24个数字，仅此而已。
Now I can compute neighbors.
现在我可以计算邻居了。
Does that make sense?
那有意义吗？
AUDIENCE: I think you have all the permutations.
听众：我认为您可以进行所有排列。
PROFESSOR: So there are six moves, right?
教授：所以有六个动作，对吗？
AUDIENCE: Yeah, but then it's right.
听众：是的，但是那是对的。
Oh yeah--
哦耶 -
PROFESSOR: If I take a configuration,
教授：如果我进行配置，
and I apply the permutation for this move,
我将这一排列应用于此动作，
I'm going to get a new configuration,
我将获得一个新的配置，
and that's its neighbor.
那是它的邻居。
So if I apply the permutation for LC 4,
因此，如果我将置换应用于LC 4，
left clockwise to this configuration,
顺时针向左转到此配置，
I get the new configuration.
我得到了新的配置。
So all I need to do is hard code those configurations,
所以我要做的就是硬编码这些配置，
and then I'm done.
然后我就完成了。
I can compute neighbors.
我可以计算邻居。
But that's a lot of typing.
但这需要大量输入。
I don't want to type as much.
我不想输入太多。
I want to reduce my burden a little bit.
我想减轻一点负担。
And we can do that by noticing that some moves are associated
我们可以通过注意一些动作来做到这一点
with some other moves.
和其他一些动作。
So, if I go left clockwise move, that's
所以，如果我顺时针左移，那就是
the inverse of a left counterclockwise move.
逆时针向左移动的反方向。
So, if given the permutation, I could compute its inverse,
因此，如果给出了排列，我可以计算其逆，
then I wouldn't have to type as many permutations.
那么我就不必键入太多的排列。
Right?
对？
Why do I care about that?
我为什么要在乎呢？
Did anyone take 6004?
有人拿过6004吗？
Remember?
记得？
So at some lab, which is the dreaded beta lab,
因此，在一个可怕的Beta实验室中，
you have to write the control block for a processor, right?
您必须为处理器编写控制块，对吗？
And that's a lot of zeros and 1's that you have to type.
这是您必须输入的很多零和1。
And if you get one wrong, good luck to [INAUDIBLE].
如果您弄错了，请[听不清]。
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
[插入语音]
AUDIENCE: 18 wide and 64 tall.
听众：18宽64高。
PROFESSOR: I know.
教授：我知道。
AUDIENCE: Copy and paste like.
听众：复制并粘贴。
AUDIENCE: Yeah, and copy paste.
听众：是的，然后复制粘贴。
[INAUDIBLE]
[听不清]
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
Bad memory.
记性不好。
Let's move on.
让我们继续。
So two good news, two pieces of good news.
所以有两个好消息，有两个好消息。
One, some of these are redundant in our case, two,
一，在我们的案例中，其中有些是多余的，二，
we wrote everything for you, so you don't have to write them,
我们为您编写了所有内容，因此您不必编写它们，
we're just teaching you how we did them,
我们只是在教你如何做，
because the inverse of a permutation is cool
因为排列的逆很酷
and I think it's a good concept to know.
我认为这是一个很好的概念。
So let's look at how a permutation looks
因此，让我们看一下排列的外观
like and compute its inverse and then move on
喜欢并计算其逆，然后继续
to other nice problems.
其他好的问题。
OK so let's take a presentation of five elements,
好，让我们介绍五个要素，
not going to go to 24 on the board here.
这里不会去董事会的24。
3, 5, 1, 2, 4.
3、5、1、2、4
This is how permutations look like in math mode.
这就是数学模式下的排列方式。
If you want to be more explicit, you
如果您想更加明确，
can add a row numbers above.
可以在上面添加行号。
And this is a bit more explicit about what a permutation does.
这一点对置换的作用更为明确。
So permutation takes an input list, let's say a b c d e.
因此，排列需要一个输入列表，比方说abcd e。
And for this is an output list, according to the recipe that
这是一个输出列表，根据配方
you see here .
你看这里。
So this pretty much says, the first element of the output
这就是说，输出的第一个元素
is the third element of the input.
是输入的第三个元素。
The second element of the output is the fifth element
输出的第二个元素是第五个元素
in the input.
在输入中。
Wait, this is the wrong permutation.
等等，这是错误的排列。
It doesn't look as pretty, so I'm changing the permutation.
它看起来并不漂亮，所以我正在更改排列。
The third element of the output is the first element
输出的第三个元素是第一个元素
in the input.
在输入中。
The fourth element of the output is which letter?
输出的第四个元素是哪个字母？
So which letter?
那是哪封信？
AUDIENCE: Oh. [INAUDIBLE]
听众：哦。 [听不清]
PROFESSOR: And the fifth element of the output is which letter?
教授：输出的第五个元素是哪个字母？
AUDIENCE: Did you mean to get c instead of a?
听众：您是要得到c而不是a吗？
No.
没有。
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
That would make more sense, wouldn't it?
那会更有意义，不是吗？
Thank you.
谢谢。
OK.
好。
So if this is permutation pi, then this
所以如果这是排列pi
is the effect of applying pi to this original list.
将pi应用于此原始列表的效果。
Now the inverse of a permutation by minus 1
现在减去-1的排列的逆
is another bunch of arrows, and what I want to do
是另一束箭，我想做什么
is, if I take this, which is the output of pi,
是，如果我将其作为pi的输出，
and I run it through these arrows,
然后我通过这些箭头
I want to get back a b c d e.
我想找回abcd e。
So I want to undo the effect of pi.
所以我想撤销pi的作用。
OK.
好。
How do I compute this inverse?
如何计算此逆？
How do I compute pi minus 1 given pi?
如何计算给定的pi减去1？
AUDIENCE: Wait, you're giving us the initial,
听众：等等，您是给我们提供初始的，
when we start with c d a e b?
什么时候开始使用cdaeb？
PROFESSOR: You only start with this.
教授：您只能从此开始。
This doesn't matter at all.
没关系。
A different list would get different results.
不同的列表将得到不同的结果。
So this is the permutation, and I want pi to the minus 1.
所以这是排列，我希望pi为负1。
AUDIENCE: So you take the value.
听众：所以您认为有价值。
So you have 3 4 1 5 2.
所以你有3 4 1 5 2
So the value at index 1 you put that index,
因此，将索引1的值放在该索引上，
that index has a value of index 3, et cetera.
该索引的值为3，等等。
AUDIENCE: So c would go to position 1?
听众：那么c会转到位置1？
AUDIENCE: Wait.
听众：等等。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
AUDIENCE: Is it true that you can run pi,
听众：您可以运行pi吗，
so the number of times it will eventually equal pi inverse?
那么它最终等于pi逆的次数是多少？
PROFESSOR: Yes, but that's complicated algebra
教授：是的，但是那是复杂的代数
to prove that.
证明这一点。
AUDIENCE: Not forget that.
听众：别忘了。
Just like make that [INAUDIBLE] thing that you made
就像使您所做的[音频不清晰]
and sort of flip it.
并进行翻转。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
I like that.
我喜欢。
So 34152, 1 2 3 4 5.
所以34152，1 2 3 4 5。
Except this doesn't look very pretty,
除非看起来不太漂亮，
so I need to sort them again, right?
所以我需要再次对它们进行排序，对吗？
So 1 3, 2 5, 3 1, 4 2, 5 4.
所以1 3，2 5，3 1，4 2，5 4。
Right?
对？
Did you guys come up with it now?
你们现在想出来了吗？
Congrats.
恭喜。
So this is good.
所以这很好。
This is how you compute an inverse.
这就是您计算逆的方式。
Let's figure out why you compute an inverse that way.
让我们弄清楚为什么以这种方式计算逆。
Let's look at b.
让我们看一下b。
So b starts out at position 2, right?
那么b从第2位开始吧？
And then pi of 5 equals 2, which means that, after applying 5,
然后pi等于5等于2，这意味着应用5之后，
b is going to go to position 5.
b将转到位置5。
So pi inverse has to take b and put it where?
所以pi逆必须取b并将其放在哪里？
Back to 2, right?
回到2，对不对？
Otherwise it's not a good inverse.
否则，它不是一个很好的逆。
So pi inverse of 2.
因此pi为2的倒数。
So the second element in the output
所以输出中的第二个元素
has to be which element in the input?
必须是输入中的哪个元素？
5, right?
5，对吗？
Otherwise, this wouldn't undo the effect of pi.
否则，这不会消除pi的影响。
So if you write out our permutation and split
因此，如果您写出我们的排列和分割
the index and the value, we get the inverse permutation.
索引和值，我们得到逆排列。
So you can compute that with a couple of lines of Python code.
因此，您可以使用几行Python代码进行计算。
OK.
好。
So this lets us now compute some of the permutations there.
因此，这使我们现在可以计算那里的一些排列。
So we only have to type up two, three, four,
所以我们只需要输入2、3、4，
or something like that.
或类似的东西。
It's a bit nicer and you guys don't
更好一点，你们不要
have to type up any, because we gave them to you.
必须输入任何内容，因为我们已将它们提供给您。
Aren't we nice?
我们不是很好吗？
All right.
好吧。
Any questions about permutations or Rubik's cubes?
对排列或魔方有任何疑问吗？
AUDIENCE: Wait, so to get high inverse
听众：等等，所以要得到高反比
based off those numbers, you just-- well,
根据这些数字，您-
it's the same thing.
这是同一件事。
Wait, but 5 got flipped.
等待，但是5被翻转了。
Or you think the maybe if the inverse of that matrix then?
还是您认为该矩阵的倒数呢？
PROFESSOR: So you take these two and you flip them, right?
教授：那么，您把这两个拿倒，就对了吗？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: And then you keep these bound, but you sort them.
教授：然后，您将它们绑定，但将它们排序。
2 5, 3 1, 4, no-- 3 5 1 2 4.
2 5、3 1、4，否-3 5 1 2 4。
AUDIENCE: Oh they're still based off the top row?
听众：哦，他们仍然排在第一位吗？
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
AUDIENCE: Oh, OK.
听众：哦，好。
AUDIENCE: Wait, how did he get the second one?
听众：等等，他是怎么得到第二个的？
AUDIENCE: Based off the top row.
听众：基于第一行。
PROFESSOR: So you sort this one, but you keep the bonds,
教授：因此，您可以对此进行排序，但是您可以保持联系，
so 3 ends up here and it gives it 1, 4 ends up here
所以3结束于此处，它得到1，1，4结束于此处
and it gives us 2.
它给了我们2。
OK.
好。
So this make sense?
所以这有意义吗？
Good.
好。
We're remembering that, that's good.
我们记得这一点，这很好。
Now let's talk about a problem.
现在让我们谈一个问题。
So this is a Rubik's cube, this is how it works.
这就是魔方，这就是它的工作原理。
Hopefully we will remember how to solve game.
希望我们会记住如何解决游戏。
Let's try to solve StarCraft Well,
让我们尝试解决《星际争霸》，
of course we're going to cheat.
当然，我们要作弊。
We're going to solve a simpler version of StarCraft
我们将解决一个更简单的《星际争霸》版本
because it turns out you can't really solve StarCraft
因为事实证明您无法真正解决《星际争霸》
with the computers that we have now.
与我们现在拥有的计算机。
So let's make a few simplifying assumptions.
因此，让我们做一些简化的假设。
Who play StarCraft, by the way?
顺便说一下，谁在玩《星际争霸》？
Two?
二？
OK.
好。
So you guys, please pay attention
所以你们请注意
to the simplifying assumptions, because this
简化的假设，因为
isn't real StarCraft.
不是真正的《星际争霸》。
It's a lot easier, so that we can build a problem out of it.
这要容易得多，因此我们可以从中解决问题。
All right.
好吧。
So we're going to play with a race called Zerg.
因此，我们将参加一场名为Zerg的比赛。
And so the idea of StarCraft is you build an army
因此，《星际争霸》的构想就是你组建一支军队
and then you take this army and you
然后你带着这支军队，你
destroy your opponent, nice and simple.
消灭对手，好而简单。
Good old violent games.
好老的暴力游戏。
So we're going to look at the build order part of the game.
因此，我们将研究游戏的构建顺序部分。
So the build order is the opening strategy and it takes
因此，构建顺序是开放策略，它需要
care of the building process, so it's the strategy that says,
关心构建过程，因此策略就是这样，
what are you going to build and when,
您打算建造什么，何时建造，
in order to come up with an army as quickly as possible?
为了尽快出兵？
So the main goal is to amass an army quickly and then take
所以主要目标是迅速集结一支军队，然后采取
that army and destroy the opponent.
那支军队消灭了对手。
And yes, I know, not real life StarCraft,
是的，我知道，不是现实生活中的《星际争霸》，
but let's go with it.
但是，让我们继续吧。
OK, so these are the rules in our toy StarCraft
好，这些是我们《玩具星际争霸》中的规则
And the Zerg is started with a building called the hatchery.
虫族始于一栋名为孵化场的建筑。
And out of a hatchery-- the currency of the game,
在孵化场之外-游戏的货币，
by the way, is minerals.
顺便说一下，是矿物质。
We'll write that down as dollars.
我们将其记为美元。
So out of a hatchery you can build a drone
因此，在孵化场之外，您可以建造无人机
by spending 50 minerals.
花费了50种矿物质
You can build an overlord by spending 100,
您可以花费100来建立一个霸主，
or you can build a Zergling by spending 50.
或者您可以花费50来打造一只Zergling。
All right, what do each of these do?
好吧，这些分别做什么？
A drone harvests minerals for you, so it's a worker.
无人机为您收获矿物质，所以它是一名工人。
So, for every drone that you have,
因此，对于您拥有的每架无人机，
you get eight minerals a second.
你每秒得到八种矿物质。
So drone gets you eight minerals a second.
因此，无人机每秒可以为您提供八种矿物质。
As Zergling is your attack unit, so this
由于虫族是您的攻击单位，因此
is the guy that you want to build in the end.
到底是你想建立的那个人。
So this destroys your opponents.
因此，这会摧毁您的对手。
I don't know how to make a nice icon for that, so big
我不知道该怎么做一个好图标
smiley green.
笑脸绿色。
This makes it happy.
这让它高兴。
All right.
好吧。
Overlords help you control your units,
霸主可以帮助您控制自己的单位，
so drones and Zerglings are units.
因此，无人机和Zerglings是单位。
You can't build-- for every eight units that you build,
您无法建立-每建立八个单位，
you have to have an overlord.
你必须有一个霸主。
Otherwise, you can't build more units
否则，您将无法建造更多单位
until you build overlords.
直到您建立霸主。
So if you have eight drones, you can't build a ninth on one
因此，如果您有八架无人驾驶飞机，那么您就无法在其中一架上建立第九架
you build an overlord.
你建立一个霸主。
If you have eight drones and these eight Zerglings,
如果您有八架无人机和这八只幼虫，
you have to build a second overlord
你必须建立第二个霸主
to be able to build more units.
能够建造更多的单位。
So one overlord can help you control eight units.
因此，一位霸主可以帮助您控制八个单位。
In order to build a Zergling, which
为了建立一只Zergling，
is what you want to do in the end,
到底是你想做的
because these are the attack units, you need to spend $50,
因为这些是攻击单元，您需要花费50美元，
and you also need to have one building called
而且您还需要有一栋名为
a spawning pool.
产卵池。
You what?
你什么？
All right.
好吧。
So how do you build that spawning pool?
那么如何建立产卵池呢？
Drones can work for you, but they can also
无人机可以为您服务，但他们也可以
transform into buildings.
转变成建筑物。
So a drone mutates into a building, and after it mutates,
因此，无人驾驶飞机变异到建筑物中，然后变异，
it doesn't work for you anymore, by the way, so no more
顺便说一句，它不再对您有用
minerals.
矿物质。
So a drone can mutate into the spawning pool for 200 minerals,
这样一架无人驾驶飞机可以变异进入产卵池，容纳200种矿物质，
I think.
我认为。
It can mutate into a hatchery.
它可以变异为孵化场。
That's the same thing that you have up here for,
这就是您要在这里做的事情，
how much is it?
多少钱？
$450.
$ 450。
And it can mutate into an evolution chamber
它可以变异为进化室
that we'll talk about soon, for $400.
我们将很快讨论，价格为400美元。
OK.
好。
Why do we care about having more than one hatchery?
我们为什么要考虑拥有多个孵化场？
One hatchery can build one unit per second, no more than that.
一个孵化场每秒可以建造一个单位，仅此而已。
So once you have a lot of drones and you're
所以一旦你有很多无人机，你就
making a lot of money, you need to have a lot of hatcheries
赚很多钱，你需要有很多孵化场
so that you can spend the money.
这样您就可以花钱了。
Our goal is not to amass money, it's to build units, right?
我们的目标不是积累资金，而是建立单位，对吧？
So money doesn't help you, I'm going
所以钱对你没有帮助，我要
to spend it as fast as possible.
尽快花费。
OK.
好。
An evolution chamber lets you build-- let's
进化室让您建立-让我们
you upgrade research to technologies.
您将研究升级为技术。
And these technologies aren't like badges.
这些技术不像徽章。
Once you get them, you keep them.
一旦获得它们，就保留它们。
So you can research an attack upgrade
这样您就可以研究攻击升级
and you can research a defense upgrade.
您可以研究防御升级。
They're both 1,000 minerals, but you only have to do it once.
它们都是1,000种矿物质，但您只需要做一次。
Why do I care about these?
我为什么要关心这些？
They decide how strong your Zerglings are.
他们决定您的幼虫有多强壮。
So, given a Zergling, at the beginning of the game,
因此，在游戏开始时，如果给一只幼虫，
you don't have the attack upgrade,
您没有攻击升级，
and you don't have a defense upgrade.
而且您没有防御升级。
So the Zerglings attack is 1.
因此，幼虫攻击为1。
If you research the attack upgrade,
如果您研究攻击升级，
but you haven't researched the defense one,
但是您还没有研究过防御
their total power is 133.
他们的总力量是133。
If you research the defense upgrade, but not the attack
如果您研究防御升级，而不是攻击
upgrade, their total power is 1.2.
升级，它们的总功率为1.2。
And after your research both of them, their total power is 2.
经过两个人的研究，它们的总强度为2。
Again, oversimplifying.
再次，过于简化。
So, we have to build an army that's as powerful as possible.
因此，我们必须建立一支尽可能强大的军队。
So in the end you want to have both of these researched.
因此，最终您需要对这两项进行研究。
All right.
好吧。
Now there's one more limitation, that is,
现在还有一个限制，那就是
you cannot control more than 200 of these units total,
您总共不能控制200个以上的单元，
because even if you have a lot of overlords,
因为即使你有很多霸主，
your brain isn't immensely huge, so you can only control 200
你的大脑不是很大，所以你只能控制2​​00
units.
单位。
So we want to build these 200 units as fast as possible.
因此，我们希望尽快构建这200个单元。
And out of these 200 units, we want
在这200个单位中，我们要
to have at least 150 Zerglings.
至少有150只幼虫。
If you build 200 drones, you're not
如果您建造200架无人机，
going to attack your opponent with that,
以此来攻击你的对手，
those aren't very useful.
这些不是很有用。
But you need some drones in order to make money,
但是你需要一些无人机才能赚钱，
so you need the balance.
所以你需要平衡。
So the goal is to get to 200 units as quickly as possible,
因此，目标是尽快达到200个单位，
and at least 150 Zergs.
至少150虫。
Yes?
是？
Evolution chamber.
进化室。
Easy, that's too much.
很简单，太多了。
OK.
好。
So how do we solve this?
那么我们该如何解决呢？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: So how do we solve this?
教授：那我们该如何解决呢？
AUDIENCE: Watch the pros play.
观众：观看专业人士的比赛。
PROFESSOR: Well, they're going to play real StarCraft this
教授：好吧，他们将扮演真正的《星际争霸》
is toy StarCraft this is six-level 6 StarCraft so it's
是玩具星际争霸这是6级6星际争霸，所以它是
not going to work.
不上班。
But there is a simple strategy, because I
但是有一个简单的策略，因为我
haven't added one last constraint.
尚未添加最后一个约束。
AUDIENCE: Lets me guess.
听众：让我猜。
PROFESSOR: No.
教授：不。
It's going to be harassing your enemy.
这会骚扰你的敌人。
But if you don't have to harass your enemy intuitively
但是如果您不必直观地骚扰敌人
and build your economy first, so first
首先建立您的经济
build your drones and hatcheries,
建立您的无人机和孵化场，
and then pop out Zerglings, right?
然后弹出幼虫，对吗？
So there's a greedy strategy.
因此，有一个贪婪的策略。
If you spend about an hour with a sheet of paper,
如果您用一张纸花一个小时左右，
you can realize what is the right order
你可以意识到什么是正确的顺序
to build drones and hatcheries and overlords,
建造无人机，孵化场和霸主，
so that you get to a nice big economy, and then, Bam!
这样您就可以拥有一个不错的大经济体，然后Bam！
Build Zerglings.
建造幼虫。
Once you get to 50 drones, you start build Zerglings
一旦达到50架无人机，就可以开始建造Zerglings
as fast as possible.
尽可能快。
So this is a greedy strategy, you
所以这是一个贪婪的策略
don't need to do a lot of work for that.
不需要为此做很多工作。
So we want to make things more interesting.
因此，我们希望使事情变得更有趣。
So in order to make things more interesting,
因此，为了使事情变得更有趣，
the game time goes in seconds.
游戏时间以秒为单位。
Everything that we had here is in seconds.
我们在这里拥有的一切都在几秒钟内。
Every two minutes, so two minutes, which is 120 seconds.
每两分钟，即两分钟，即120秒。
So every two minutes I want to assemble
所以每两分钟我要组装一次
a small pack of Zerglings and send them
一小袋幼虫并将其发送
to the enemy to harass them.
对敌人进行骚扰。
And the Antonio enemy will defend themselves
安东尼奥的敌人会保卫自己
and they will destroy my Zerglings,
他们会摧毁我的幼虫，
but they won't be able to focus on the game very well.
但他们将无法很好地专注于游戏。
So I need to do this in order to have a good chance to win.
所以我需要这样做，以便有一个很好的获胜机会。
If I don't do this, my strategy is invalid.
如果我不这样做，则我的策略无效。
AUDIENCE: Does the enemy, does it do that to us as well?
听众：敌人是否也对我们这样做？
PROFESSOR: No.
教授：不。
We're sending them facts.
我们正在向他们发送事实。
We are going to have a really fast strategy, because we're
我们将有一个非常快速的策略，因为我们
computing the optimal strategy, so they're not
计算最佳策略，所以他们没有
going to have time.
要有时间。
They're going to be fighting us off.
他们将与我们抗争。
OK, how many Zerglings do I send?
好，我要寄几只幼虫？
I have to send enough Zerglings so that the attack
我必须派出足够的幼虫，以便攻击
power at minutes 2m is 6 times log 1 plus m.
2m分钟的功率是log 1 plus m的6倍。
You knew there has to be some mapping there.
您知道那里必须有一些映射。
So the reason for this is, let's look at the first two minutes.
因此，原因是，让我们看一下前两分钟。
After two minutes, if we haven't researched any upgrades,
两分钟后，如果我们还没有研究任何升级，
we need to send this in six Zerglings.
我们需要在六个幼虫中寄出。
If we researched both upgrades, we only
如果我们研究了两个升级，我们只会
need to send in three Zerglings.
需要发送三个幼虫。
If we researched one of the upgrades,
如果我们研究了其中一种升级，
we need to send in five Zerglings.
我们需要寄出五个幼虫。
So this is the total attack power,
这就是总的攻击力
not the numbers are of Zerglings that we need to send.
而不是我们需要发送的幼虫的数量。
AUDIENCE: And is minutes?
听众：是分钟吗？
PROFESSOR: Actually, it's basically
教授：其实，基本上
which attack wave you're doing, so every two minutes.
您正在执行哪个攻击波，因此每两分钟一次。
AUDIENCE: Oh, OK.
听众：哦，好。
So the first one is m equals zero.
所以第一个是m等于零。
PROFESSOR: And 1.
教授：还有1。
That is not the one attacking right in the beginning
那不是一开始就进攻的权利
when we don't have Zerglings.
当我们没有幼虫时。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: Equals 1, n equals 2, n equals 3, so on and so forth.
教授：等于1，n等于2，n等于3，依此类推。
AUDIENCE: How did you get that formula?
听众：你是怎么得到这个公式的？
OK.
好。
PROFESSOR: Is it making your life hard?
教授：这使您的生活艰难吗？
Would that be logged base 2, or is that log base 10?
是以2为基础记录还是以10为基础记录？
PROFESSOR: Sure, log base 2.
教授：好的，以2为底的对数。
Fine.
精细。
OK, so how are we going to solve this?
好，那我们该如何解决呢？
Intuitively, how did we solve all the game
直观地讲，我们如何解决所有游戏
problems, all the problems recently?
问题，最近所有问题？
What are we going to do?
我们会做什么？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: So the first thing we're
教授：所以我们第一件事
going to build a graph, right?
要建立一个图形，对不对？
AUDIENCE: Yeah.
听众：是的。
PROFESSOR: So build a graph.
教授：因此，建立一个图表。
The vertices are the states of the game,
顶点是游戏的状态，
so a vertex shows me what state I'm in
所以一个顶点告诉我我处于什么状态
and an edge shows possible moves that I do.
边缘显示了我可能执行的操作。
So what I need to keep track in the vertex, what's my state?
所以我需要在顶点处跟踪，我的状态是什么？
AUDIENCE: How much money you have, and how many units
听众：您有多少钱，有多少单位
you have?
你有？
And maybe how fast you're making money?
也许您赚钱有多快？
AUDIENCE: Oh, unless the states, are
听众：哦，除非有州，否则
states-- they're not movable?
状态-它们不动吗？
Oh, I guess they could be moveable [INAUDIBLE] could
哦，我想它们可能是可移动的[听不清]
do nothing, in the next second, right?
在下一秒什么都不做，对吧？
PROFESSOR: So you're saying you need to keep track of time,
教授：所以您是说您需要跟踪时间，
too?
太？
AUDIENCE: I don't know.
听众：我不知道。
PROFESSOR: OK so maybe time.
教授：好的，也许是时间。
What else?
还有什么？
AUDIENCE: Badge [INAUDIBLE] thing.
听众：徽章[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: OK so upgrades.
教授：好的，请升级。
You said units, I'm going to say buildings.
您说的是单位，我要说的是建筑物。
AUDIENCE: Wait, is Zergling is a building?
听众：等等，Zergling是建筑物吗？
PROFESSOR: A Zergling is a unit, so-
教授：Zergling是一个单元，所以-
AUDIENCE: Overlords.
听众：霸主。
PROFESSOR: Unit, unit, unit.
教授：单位，单位，单位。
Building, building, building, upgrade, upgrade.
建筑，建筑，建筑，升级，升级。
So let's see how are we going to keep track of them.
因此，让我们看看如何跟踪它们。
That's a good point.
那是个很好的观点。
We started looking at units, we started looking at units.
我们开始查看单位，开始查看单位。
So how do I keep track of my units?
那我该如何追踪我的单位呢？
What I need to know?
我需要知道什么？
AUDIENCE: The number of drones, overlords, servlings.
听众：无人驾驶飞机，霸主和服务的数量。
PROFESSOR: Droids, drones, overlords, Zerglings.
教授：机器人，无人机，霸主，幼虫。
OK.
好。
How about buildings?
建筑物呢？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE] PHEC--
听众：[听不清] PHEC--
PROFESSOR: Almost.
教授：差不多了。
So I want to know the number of hatcheries,
所以我想知道孵化场的数量，
because this is how fast I can produce.
因为这是我可以生产的速度。
But then how many spawning pools am I going to build?
但是我要建造多少个产卵池呢？
Good.
好。
So that was StarCraft player 1.
那就是星际争霸1。
Once you have a spawning pool, you can build Zerglings,
有了产卵池后，就可以构建Zerglings，
there's no reason to build more than one.
没有理由建造不止一个。
So a spawning pool is going to be like a badge.
因此，产卵池将像徽章一样。
Once you build it, you have it, you're done.
一旦构建完成，就完成了。
So it's Boolean.
所以它是布尔值。
AUDIENCE: Wait, what's a spawning pool again?
听众：等等，又是什么产卵池？
PROFESSOR: So a spawning pool is something
教授：产卵池是什么
that you build off a drone and once you have it,
建造一架无人驾驶飞机，一旦拥有它，
you can build Zerglings from a hatchery.
您可以从孵化场建造Zerglings。
So that's all it does.
这就是全部。
AUDIENCE: Why would you want two if you
听众：如果要，你为什么要两个
can build four Zerglings?
可以造四个幼虫？
PROFESSOR: So the spawning pool doesn't build a Zergling.
教授：因此产卵池不会造出Zergling。
See, the hatchery builds the Zerglings.
看到，孵化场建造了幼虫。
So the spawning pool is just there.
因此产卵池就在那里。
You need to have it to cross the edge.
您需要让它越过边缘。
Otherwise you can't.
否则，你不能。
AUDIENCE: OK.
听众：好的。
I understand.
我明白。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So what else for buildings?
那么建筑物还有什么呢？
Whether you have it or not, right?
是否拥有它，对吗？
OK.
好。
How about upgrades?
升级怎么样？
[INAUDIBLE] a u, d u.
[听不清] au，d u。
PROFESSOR: So two flags, a u, d u.
教授：所以，两个标志au，d u。
Cool.
凉。
So now we have the thorny issues of money and time.
因此，现在我们面临着金钱和时间的棘手问题。
Let's say that we're going to have some sort of approximation
假设我们将要进行某种近似
that's going to allow us to not keep track of money,
这将使我们无法跟踪金钱，
because money is-- you can have a lot of money,
因为钱是-您可以拥有很多钱，
so that will give us an explosion of states.
这样一来，我们的国家便会激增。
So we're going to assume that we're spending money
所以我们假设我们要花钱
as fast as possible, because that's
尽可能快，因为那是
what you usually want to do.
您通常想要做什么。
AUDIENCE: So should your money always be zero then?
听众：那你的钱应该永远为零吗？
PROFESSOR: Almost.
教授：差不多了。
It's very close to that.
这非常接近。
So you start off with no money.
因此，您一开始就没有钱。
You accumulate money, then you're
你积累金钱，然后你
going to issue some build orders and build something.
将发出一些建造订单并建造一些东西。
And your money's going to drop, maybe
而且您的钱将会减少，也许
to zero, maybe to almost zero.
零，也许几乎为零。
Then you wait to accumulate more money,
然后，您等待积累更多的钱，
issue another build order.
发出另一个构建命令。
Wait to accumulate more money, hopefully it goes faster now.
等待积累更多的钱，希望它现在能更快。
Issue another build order.
发出另一个构建命令。
We're going to approximate that every time we
每次我们都要近似
issue a build order, so every time we
发出建造订单，所以每次我们
tell our things to build something,
告诉我们要建造的东西，
the money will drop to zero.
钱将降为零。
So that doesn't mean you can only build one thing
所以这并不意味着你只能建造一件事
and then your money drops to zero.
然后您的钱降为零。
If you wait for a few seconds and then you
如果您等待几秒钟，然后
have two hatcheries and tell both of them to build drones,
有两个孵化场，并告诉他们两个建造无人机，
you build two drones and then your money goes to zero.
你造了两架无人机，然后你的钱变成了零。
So that means that if we model our states carefully,
因此，这意味着，如果我们仔细建模我们的状态，
we don't have to keep track of money.
我们不必跟踪钱。
AUDIENCE: You should probably keep track of time.
听众：您可能应该跟踪时间。
AUDIENCE: Actually keep track of the rate
听众：实际上跟踪汇率
you're gathering though, right?
你在聚会吧？
PROFESSOR: So what's the rate that you're gathering?
教授：那么您的集会率是多少？
AUDIENCE: It's the number of--
听众：这是-
AUDIENCE: Oh [INAUDIBLE] drones, yeah. [INAUDIBLE], OK.
听众：哦[听不清]无人机，是的。 [听不清]，好的。
PROFESSOR: So this multiplied by 8%.
教授：所以这乘以8％。
AUDIENCE: So we should keep track of time.
听众：所以我们应该跟踪时间。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So how would we solve it if we keep track of time?
那么，如果我们跟踪时间，该如何解决呢？
AUDIENCE: You multiply
听众：你乘
AUDIENCE: Can you do that layer thing again?
听众：你能再做一次分层的事情吗？
Where is that?
哪里是？
PROFESSOR: So you're going to have-- so what's a layer?
教授：那么您将拥有-那么什么是层？
AUDIENCE: Actually, never mind.
听众：其实，没关系。
AUDIENCE: I want to know what a layer is.
听众：我想知道什么是图层。
PROFESSOR: Sorry?
教授：对不起？
AUDIENCE: I want to know what a layer is.
听众：我想知道什么是图层。
PROFESSOR: So last time we-- we solved problems by saying that,
教授：所以，上次我们说的是解决问题的方法，
so we had the graph of streets.
所以我们有了街道图。
We had a highway graph.
我们有一个公路图。
And that was a 2D graph.
那是2D图。
And we made it into a 3D graph by adding time
我们通过添加时间将其制作成3D图形
as a third dimension.
作为第三维。
So we had layers, where each layer was,
所以我们有几层，每一层在哪里，
said that you're at a point in the graph
说你在图中的一点
at a certain point in time.
在某个时间点。
So there's a layer 4 times 0, layer 4 time 1,
因此，有一个4乘以0的层，4乘以1的层，
so on and so forth.
等等等等。
And you start at time 0 and kept going up the graph.
并且您从时间0开始，并一直在上升。
AUDIENCE: You have a flag that says,
听众：您有一个标语，
I've just purchased something?
我刚买东西吗？
Because that way then you'll know that you've completely
因为那样一来，您就会知道自己已经完全
exhausted your-- that maybe that will tell you
精疲力竭-也许那会告诉你
that you can't buy anything for awhile, right?
暂时不能买东西，对吧？
Because if we're not keeping track of money then
因为如果我们不跟踪钱的话
we should know [INAUDIBLE].
我们应该知道[听不清]。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
So that's a good point.
这是一个好点。
So if I have-- so suppose here I have to wait for five seconds
所以如果我有-假设在这里我必须等待五秒钟
to get enough money to do a move.
以获得足够的钱来搬家。
If I keep track of time in my state and I
如果我跟踪自己所在州的时间，
have five things here.
这里有五件事。
I also have to keep track of money, right?
我也要跟踪钱，对吧？
I have to know how much money I'm getting,
我要知道我能赚多少钱
so that I know where I'm buying things.
这样我就知道我在哪里买东西。
On the other hand, in this case, if I
另一方面，在这种情况下，如果我
keep track of both time and money as states,
保持时间和金钱状态，
I can implement a precise strategy.
我可以执行一个精确的策略。
I don't need this approximation.
我不需要这个近似值。
If I do that, then what search algorithm would I use?
如果这样做，我将使用哪种搜索算法？
So if I have time in states, so each vertex in my note
因此，如果我有时间在状态中，那么笔记中的每个顶点
says that I get from some states to some other state
说我从某些州到其他州
in one unit of time.
在一个时间单位内。
What algorithm do I use to search for my strategy?
我用什么算法搜索我的策略？
Yeah.
是的
Why do I use BFS?
为什么要使用BFS？
AUDIENCE: Because every edge has the same weight.
听众：因为每个边缘都有相同的权重。
PROFESSOR: Every edge has the same weight, right?
教授：每个边缘都有相同的重量，对吗？
So if we keep track of time, then
因此，如果我们跟踪时间，
we-- we keep track of time, we keep track of money,
我们-我们跟踪时间，我们跟踪金钱，
we use BFS, we have a solution.
我们使用BFS，我们有一个解决方案。
So.
所以。
Let's try to not do it, either of these.
让我们尝试不做任何一个。
If I don't want to keep track of time
如果我不想跟踪时间
and I don't want to keep track of money,
而且我不想跟踪钱，
what would an edge be?
边缘会是什么？
If I want to say that, hey, this is a state and this is a state.
如果我要说的话，嘿，这是一个状态，这是一个状态。
What should be the edge connecting them.
连接它们的边缘应该是什么？
AUDIENCE: What other item you got is.
听众：您还有什么其他东西。
AUDIENCE: Is that after a second?
听众：那是一秒钟之后吗？
PROFESSOR: So the distance between these
教授：所以这些之间的距离
won't be a second, right?
一秒钟不会吧？
If I have to wait for five seconds to
如果我要等五秒钟
accumulate enough to issue this build order
积累足够发出此构建订单
that would get me the state then--
那会让我有状态-
AUDIENCE: The time you have to wait?
听众：您该等什么时间？
PROFESSOR: So that's what I would put on an edge.
教授：那就是我的优势。
So this way I don't have to keep track of money,
这样我就不必跟踪钱了
I don't have to keep track of time.
我不必跟踪时间。
So the graph is smaller.
因此该图较小。
So I can look into bigger graphs.
因此，我可以研究更大的图表。
If I do this, what algorithm do I use?
如果执行此操作，应使用哪种算法？
To find my strategy?
找到我的策略？
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE].
听众：[听不清]。
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
[插入语音]
PROFESSOR: So no time, no money.
教授：所以没有时间，没有钱。
And [? extra ?].
然后[？额外？]。
So this looks reasonably easy, right?
因此，这看起来相当容易，对吧？
I mean, if you want to get from one state to another,
我的意思是，如果您想从一种状态进入另一种状态，
you see what you'd have to build,
您会看到需要构建的内容，
you see how much it costs, and you
你看它要花多少钱，你
see how much you have to wait to accumulate those resources.
看看您需要等​​待多少时间来累积这些资源。
Except there's one glitch.
除了一个小故障。
How do we deal with this?
我们该如何处理？
How do we make sure that we do our attacks on time and how do
我们如何确保我们按时进行攻击以及如何做
we know that we're-- how do we keep track of them?
我们知道我们-我们如何跟踪他们？
AUDIENCE: What is this again representing?
听众：这又代表什么？
PROFESSOR: So this is that every two minutes you
教授：这就是您每两分钟
have to have a number of Zerglings
必须有一些幼虫
that you're sending to attack the enemy.
您要发动攻击敌人。
And the number of Zerglings that you need to have
还有你需要的幼虫数量
depends on the time and it depends on the upgrades
取决于时间，取决于升级
that you got.
你得到的。
So how do we keep track of this?
那么我们如何跟踪呢？
AUDIENCE: If the edges are a function of time,
听众：如果边缘是时间的函数，
then just know that at radius 120-- at radius 120 over 5,
那么只要知道在半径120处-在半径120处，
then you'd have to send more Zerglings.
那么您将不得不发送更多的幼虫。
PROFESSOR: So what if not all the edges have the same weight.
教授：如果不是所有边缘都具有相同的权重，那该怎么办？
So let's look at how a graph looks like for a little bit.
因此，让我们看一下图形的外观。
So we're going to have an initial state,
所以我们将有一个初始状态，
say one hatchery and six drones and one overlord.
说一间孵化场，六架无人机和一架霸主。
And we want to build a new drone.
我们想建造一架新的无人机。
Say we want to build a new drone.
假设我们要建造新的无人机。
A drone costs 50 minerals.
无人机消耗50种矿物质。
We have six drones.
我们有六架无人机。
Each drone gets us eight minerals a second,
每架无人机每秒都能为我们提供八种矿物质，
so in one second we're going to get 48 minerals.
因此，在一秒钟内，我们将获得48种矿物质。
So bummer, we have to wait for two seconds to build one drone.
好可惜，我们必须等待两秒钟才能建造一架无人驾驶飞机。
And now we're going to be in the state of one hatchery, seven
现在我们要进入一个孵化场，七个孵化场
drones, one overlord.
无人机，一位霸主。
If you said we want to build a hatchery-- then
如果您说我们要建造一个孵化场-那么
we're going to need to accumulate 400 or 450.
我们将需要累积400或450。
Oh, we have to accumulate 450, using six drones, 48 minerals,
哦，我们必须使用六架无人机，48种矿物质累计450架，
so I guess nine seconds.
所以我猜是九秒
So we're going to have to wait for nine seconds
所以我们将不得不等待九秒钟
to get that money.
得到那笔钱。
And then when we build, we're going
然后当我们建造时，我们要
to spend the drone building, because it's
花无人机建造，因为它是
going to turn into a hatchery.
将变成一个孵化场。
And then we're going to end up with two hatcheries, five
然后我们将要建造两个孵化场，五个
drones, and one overlord.
无人机和一位霸主。
So edges have different weights.
因此，边缘具有不同的权重。
So I can't look at the radius in terms of number of his edges.
因此，我无法根据其边缘数量来查看半径。
AUDIENCE: Everything builds instantaneously.
听众：一切都是瞬间建立的。
PROFESSOR: Yeah, sure.
教授：是的，当然。
AUDIENCE: You could keep track of just the total distance
听众：您可以跟踪总距离
from whatever starting build you are?
从什么开始构建？
AUDIENCE: Actually, if the distance
听众：实际上，如果距离
from the origin to where you're at is a multiple of 120,
从原点到您的所在地是120的倍数，
then you should have another state
那你应该有另一个状态
that you have to [INAUDIBLE].
您必须[听不清]。
AUDIENCE: Assuming you have any drones left, hopefully you do.
听众：假设您还有任何无人机，希望可以。
PROFESSOR: So that's modeling.
教授：那就是建模。
One way of doing it is sure, model every round
确保做到这一点的一种方法是每轮建模
of the attack as one, every round of harassment
一次袭击，每一轮骚扰
is one there in the graph, and we can do it that way.
图中有一个，我们可以那样做。
Is that what you're saying?
那是你的意思吗
So you can't-- once you're at 120 seconds,
因此，一旦达到120秒，您就无法
you have to do an attack and then you get to the next layer
您必须进行攻击，然后进入下一层
in the graph.
在图中。
AUDIENCE: That makes a lot of sense.
听众：这很有道理。
AUDIENCE: Of course that's what we were thinking.
听众：当然，这就是我们的想法。
PROFESSOR: How about let's not do that.
教授：那我们就不要那样做。
How about let's represent it without layers?
让我们不用层来表示它吗？
So that's good.
这样很好。
You're getting closer to the solution.
您正在接近解决方案。
It is much better than representing every time.
这比每次都代表要好得多。
Write the number of layers this time over 120,
这次写的层数超过120，
it's a huge improvement.
这是一个巨大的进步。
Well, we can do it without any-- we can do it
好吧，我们可以一无所获-我们可以做到
without any time notion whatsoever.
没有任何时间观念。
Let's see, can I let you think about it?
让我们看看，我可以让你考虑一下吗？
Oh, I can let you think about it for 30 seconds.
哦，我可以让您考虑30秒。
So there's a key insight here that--
因此，这里有一个关键见解-
AUDIENCE: Ooh.
听众：哦。
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
AUDIENCE: [INAUDIBLE] but if you figure how much time has
听众：[听不清]，但如果您知道有多少时间
elapsed, based on the items we have
过去，根据我们拥有的项目
and our starting state, right?
还有我们的起始状态，对吗？
Because if we have two hatcheries
因为如果我们有两个孵化场
and we started with one hatchery,
我们从一个孵化场开始
we know that at least nine seconds has elapsed.
我们知道至少已经过去了9秒。
PROFESSOR: Well, so I like the first part of what you said,
教授：好，所以我喜欢您所说的第一部分，
the second part is too complicated.
第二部分太复杂了。
But we can know what time we're at.
但是我们可以知道我们几点钟了。
Why?
为什么？
AUDIENCE: Because it takes a certain amount of time
听众：因为需要一定的时间
to achieve everything, each thing.
实现每件事，每一件事。
AUDIENCE: Are we assuming that we take the shortest
观众：我们是否假设我们选的最短
path to get to each state that we're at?
到达我们所处的每个州的路径？
PROFESSOR: So we're using the extra.
教授：所以我们正在使用额外的东西。
How does the extra work?
额外的工作方式如何？
You have a queue, a priority queue.
您有一个队列，一个优先级队列。
You extract a node, you look at the neighbors.
您提取一个节点，然后查看邻居。
When you extract the node, do you
提取节点时，
know the distance to that node?
知道到那个节点的距离吗？
AUDIENCE: Can you explain?
听众：你能解释一下吗？
You ask?
你问？
PROFESSOR: I'm asking.
教授：我在问。
AUDIENCE: I know, but like the node asks and says,
听众：我知道，但是就像节点问并说的那样，
how far away are you?
你有多远
PROFESSOR: So you need to keep that in the priority queue.
教授：因此，您需要将其保留在优先级队列中。
So the extra-- the main invariant
因此，额外的-主要不变式
is that once you pull out the node,
是一旦您拉出节点，
you're not going to find any shorter path to that node.
您不会找到该节点的任何更短路径。
So you already know the shortest path.
因此，您已经知道最短的路径。
That how you sort the nodes in the priority queue.
那就是你如何排序优先队列中的节点。
So when we're at a configuration--
因此，当我们进行配置时-
Say we're at some configuration here,
假设我们在这里有一些配置，
two hatches, six drones, and five Zerglings.
两架舱口，六架无人机和五只幼虫。
We already know that, say we're at time 119 seconds.
我们已经知道，比如说我们的时间是119秒。
If what I want to do next is build another hatchery,
如果我接下来要做的是建造另一个孵化场，
then I have to wait, what, six drones, same thing as before.
然后我得等六架无人机，和以前一样。
I have to wait for nine seconds, right?
我必须等待九秒钟，对不对？
So the edge would look like this.
因此边缘看起来像这样。
And then we're going to get to three hatcheries, five
然后我们要去三个孵化场，五个
drones, five Zerglings.
无人机，五只幼虫。
This crosses a one, this crosses a two-minute boundary, right?
这越过一个，这越过了两分钟的边界，对吗？
So when I cross this boundary, I'd
所以，当我越过边界时，我会
better have enough Zerglings to do an attack.
最好有足够的幼虫来发动攻击。
Do I have enough Zerglings to do an attack?
我是否有足够的幼虫进行攻击？
No.
没有。
So is this a valid move?
那么这是一个有效的举动吗？
Is this the valid edge in our graph?
这是我们图中的有效边吗？
It's not.
不是。
So when you're at a node, you already know the time
因此，当您在节点上时，您已经知道了时间
that you need to get to that node,
您需要到达该节点，
so when you generate the neighbors,
因此，当您生成邻居时，
you can check for each edge to see
您可以检查每个边缘以查看
it crosses that 120 second game.
超过了120秒。
Now let's assume it does.
现在让我们假设它可以。
Let's see how this works and this
让我们看看这是如何工作的
is the last thing we're doing.
是我们要做的最后一件事。
So suppose you have two hatcheries, six drones,
因此，假设您有两个孵化场，六个无人机，
and eight Zerglings.
和八只幼虫。
And you're going to build that same hatchery.
您将要建立同样的孵化场。
So you're going to go past this 120 second mark.
因此，您将超过120秒。
What state are you going to end up in?
您将处于什么状态？
How many hatcheries?
多少个孵化场？
AUDIENCE: Three.
听众：三。
PROFESSOR: OK.
教授：好的。
How many drones.
几架无人机。
AUDIENCE: Five.
听众：五。
PROFESSOR: How many Zerglings.
教授：多少只幼虫。
AUDIENCE: Two.
听众：两个。
PROFESSOR: Yes.
教授：是的。
So key elements, two Zerglings, because this edge
所以关键元素，两只幼虫，因为这个优势
crosses the 120-second harassment boundary,
越过了120秒的骚扰边界，
so you have to send in six Zerglings
所以你必须送出六只幼虫
and you're going to lose them.
而你会失去他们。
So we're taking advantage of how the extra works to sort
因此，我们正在利用额外的工作方式进行排序
of generate our edges on the fly.
迅速产生我们的优势。
So we wouldn't be able to regenerate this graph,
因此我们将无法重新生成该图，
even if we wanted to have to.
即使我们想要
We have to work with the implicit representation
我们必须使用隐式表示
and, as we learn the distances to the nodes,
并且，当我们了解到节点的距离时，
the minimum distances, we also learned the edges
最小距离，我们还了解了边缘
that we have coming out of those nodes.
我们已经从那些节点出来了。
AUDIENCE: So it's kinda of like this graph that's growing
听众：有点像这张图在增长
and we're like as it gets to a certain point
而且就像到达某一点一样
we kill a bunch of paths and then it keeps on going.
我们杀死了许多路径，然后继续前进。
PROFESSOR: Yeah.
教授：是的。
Doesn't this makes sense?
这不合理吗？
So the good news is that this is like we're
好消息是，这就像我们
training you to run a 10-mile marathon,
训练您进行10英里的马拉松，
so you can run 50 meters for the test.
因此您可以跑50米进行测试。
Let's still try to get it, because I
让我们继续尝试，因为我
think it's a cool problem.
认为这是一个很酷的问题。